

Priya Singh

Frontend Developer| Exp 7+| Serving Notice Period | Last working day 1st Sep | Expert in developing Responsive & Interactive websites | Skilled in ReactJS, GraphQL, Node JS, Redux, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, SASS, and JQuery, micro-frontend

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: +91-9891811856

Email: singh.priya2908@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

• Total Experience 7 Years 5 Months

Current Location Pune

Date of Birth Mar 29, 1995Gender Female

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Redux
- Graphql
- MongoDB
- JQuery
- Photoshop
- Micro-Frontend
- Reacts Js
- Node Express
- Node.Js

LANGUAGES KNOWN

- English
- Hindi

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

SOCIAL LINKS

 https://www.linkedin.com/in/priya-singh-131b65bb/

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am looking forward to working within large enterprises in the IT sector having work locations in Pune. Currently, I'm working as an Application Developer | with 7+Years of Experience in Frontend Development | Expert in developing Responsive & Interactive websites | Skilled in CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap, SASS, React JS, JavaScript, Node JS, GraphQL, and JQuery. | B.Tech (CSE - 2016)

EDUCATION HISTORY

Doctorate

Course B.Tech(COMPUTER SCIENCE)

College Maharishi Dayanand University (MDU),

Rohtak

Year of Passing 2016 Grade 78%

Class XII

Board CBSE
Medium English
Year of Passing 2012
Grade 85-89.9%

Class X

Board Haryana Medium English Year of Passing 2010 Grade 85-89.9%

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2021 to Present

Front End Developer at IBM

Creating features for Sales and Tender Services which is an API under the hood of the Finance Reconciliation Domain. It's an in-house product that performs reconciliation across all Tesco Operating Channels and tender types. deriving liabilities for 3rd party/Non-Tesco sales and serving as a single source of truth for all sales across UK Stores.

Jul 2020 to May 2021

Software Engineer L3 at Robosoft Technologies

Working as a Frontend Developer with designation Software Engineer L3 in Paytm Project for new features using tech-stack of React JS, HTML, CSS, Javascript.

Apr 2017 to Apr 2020

Software Engineer at To The New

1) A Front End Developer who implement visual and interactive elements that users engage with through their web browser when using a web application. 2) Design mobile-based features. 3) Hands-on experience with markup languages. 4) Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, AEM Theming, Drupal theming. 5) Familiarity with browser testing and debugging. 6) In-depth understanding of the entire web development process (design, development, and deployment). 7) Knowledge of SEO principles and digital marketing GTM Scripts. 8) Familiarity with software like Zeplin, Photoshop and content management system(CMS)

Feb 2016 to Feb 2017

UI Developer at Damco Solutions

Responsible for designing and developing user interfaces for the websites, marketing banners, and Emailers.

PROJECTS

Sales Tender Services, 808 Days

STS is an API under the hood of Finance Reconciliation Domain. It's an in-house product that performs reconciliation across all Tesco Operating Channels and tender types. deriving liabilities for 3rd party/Non-Tesco sales and serving as a single source of truth for all sales across UK Stores. STS service post data to General ledger and other crucial downstream systems for Financial Accounting, Stock Analysis and Reconciliation.

IOCL Fuel Xtra Wallet, 61 Days

Scan and Pay flow at IOCL fuel pumps using Paytm app to get exciting reward points.

KaiOS Paytm, 1143 Days

Developing Paytm mini-apps in KaiOS for Jio phones

Digital Marketing, 31 Days

Implementation of Google Tag Analysis scripts for helping the Digital Marketing team for the marketing of Projects.

Brands For Less, 334 Days

The BFL Group is one of the world??s leading off-price retailer of fashion and homeware. Technologies Used: HTML, SASS, Javascript, ES6 concepts, React, Redux, Backend: Node.js

Invest India, 306 Days

It focuses on sector-specific investor targeting and the development of new partnerships to enable sustainable investments in India.

Start Up India, 273 Days

It is a flagship initiative of the Government of India, India's largest online entrepreneurship platform allows startups to network, access free tools & resources and participate in programs & challenges.

Max Life Insurance, 153 Days

It is India's leading life insurance company in India.

Do Trips, 123 Days

Revamp of Dubai Parks and Resorts

Damco Website, 153 Days

Damco Solutions Pvt Ltd info website

Nuts And Bolts, 244 Days

An Employment and Business management portal